# BRITTANIQUE HONEYGHAN

155 David Street Hagersville, ON, NOA 1H0 (647) 671-6796 brittaniqueh@gmail.com

## CAREER OBJECTIVE

Self-motivated, dedicated and enthusiastic young professional. With 5+ years of retail and customer service experience, I have had the chance to hone my interpersonal, communication, organization, and persuasive skills. In addition, I have attained clerical and administrative experience working for the Costa Law firm as clerical administrator and legal assistant. As an avid learner and researcher, I have done collaborative and independent research for the University of Toronto which has increased my knowledge in the areas of data analytics, problemsolving, ethics, and innovation. With my qualifications and skillsets, I am confident that I would make a great asset to your company.

## EDUCATION

# UNIVERSITY OF TORONTO TORONTO, ON

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) Political Science Candidate (Expected graduation Jun 2021)

- Awards & Honors: Honor Roll, Leadership, Best Student of the Month, Perfect Attendance Award, David Rayside Undergraduate Scholarship
- Extracurricular Activities: Canadian Red Cross volunteer, Nursing home volunteer

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# UNIVERSITY OF TORONTO, TORONTO, ON

Research Assistant, May 2021 - Aug 2021

- Utilized search engine software for result optimization to check and process cases for inclusion in the larger data set
- Performed basic processes of data management and analysis
- · Created weekly reports and exchanged ideas in collaborative team meetings
- Assist to produce tables, charts, and graphs that were used in project communications on the research website presentations, and in papers

#### MARCIANO, TORONTO, ON

Customer Service Assosiate, Apr 2017 - Aug 2017

- Financial Advisor and Consultant, ensured clientele received best luxury customer experience
- Maintained highest sales per hour (SPH) increasing productivity by 25% on average
- Maintained clean and organized store and collaborated as a team member to create a productive and efficient environment
- · Accurately collected payments, processed returns and exchanges and updated VIP customer loyalty

STITCHES, BRAMPTON, ON

Customer and sales specialist, Aug 2015 - Jan 2016

- Accurately and efficiently collecting payments, answering customer inquiries, accepting customer returns, exchanges as a cashier
- Health and Safety Representative, ensuring the store meets all legal expectations and actively supports occupational health and safety
- Visual merchandiser, promoting and organized products and increasing sales

# COSTA LAW FIRM, TORONTO, ON

Clerical Administration & Legal Assistant , Sep 2014 - Jun 2015

- Assisted lawyers in gathering, filing, and preparing court documents
- · Ensured clients information are entered into database accurately and confidentially
- Provided friendly, trusted, and reliable customer service

## ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Customer service & sales specialist
- Detail oriented & organized
- Excellent problem solver
- Strong written & verbal communicator
- Creative & Innovative
- Multi-tasking skills

## LICENSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

• High School Diploma

# REFERENCES

References available upon request